A sound soul dwells within a sound mind and a sound body.
Welcome to Death Weapon Meister Academy.
More commonly known as the DWMA, it stands as a defense against the forces of evil, which
would plunge the world into chaos and drag humanity to the very depths of fear and madness.
The demons known as Keishin and their insatiable hunger for destruction.
To ensure the Keishin never regained their hold on this world, this academy was founded
by the Grim Reaper, Day himself.
So basically, we're an organization that exists to protect and preserve peace.
I guess it's not exactly a typical school.
Oh well, that isn't important.
For now, let's roll up our sleeves and get to work.
washerdomen relevanable
均一ダリエル
綱反朗
つないだ魂の火が胸を刺すなら
言葉よりもっと強い響きが今聞こえるか
Thank you.
悪い夢に続いても
繋いだ魂の火が胸を刺すなら
言葉よりもっと強い響きが今聞こえるか
やっと理由は途絶びに突きつけられて
触れた瞬間の傷の分だけ確かになれる
ご視聴ありがとうございました
What more power?
More power!
That man-soul-eater, his soul
Yeah, Maka, there's no doubt about it
That dude's soul is a Kishin egg
It's pure evil
He's not human anymore
Any soul that breaks from the path of humanity and becomes evil
runs the risk of transforming into a Kishin
In the name of Lord Death, this evil must be purged
Let's collect the damaged soul and end this
Just so we're clear, Maka, this guy's turning himself into a weapon
He's the same as me that way
Of course, I look a lot cooler in my human form than he does
But being a weapon isn't what the problem is here
The problem with this guy is his soul
I know
You, serial killer Jack the Ripper
Your murdering days are done
Your soul is mine
You're winning Meister, two fighting as one
Let's go, soul
Maka, thank you for a good meal
We're almost there, aren't we?
Took us long enough, but that was number 99
So we finally collected all the Kishin souls we need
Only one thing left now
I've just gotta eat the soul of a witch
Then I'll be one of Lord Death's weapons
You're looking at the next Death Scythe
I know, as if I wasn't cool enough already, right?
Anyway, we'd better report back to Lord Death and let him know
Just write in the Death Room's number
4242-564, whenever you want to knock on Death's door
Hello, Lord Death, are you there?
Meister Maka reporting
Yeah, yeah, hello, Meister Maka
How are you doing?
How did it go?
I've just collected the 99th Kishin soul, sir
Now we just have one witch soul left to collect and we'll be done
Well done, Maka
You're proving to me just as excellent a maestro as your mother was
Hey, Soul Eater
If you even think of touching my Maka
If you lay a hand on her as a Death Scythe
No, as her father, I will freaking kill you
You got me, you little octopus head?
What are you smoking?
See how cool I am?
You think I'm gonna settle for a flat-chested girl like her?
What did you just say?
Are you trying to tell me that my Maka's not attractive?
Why haven't you made a move on her?
You're a man, Arjo!
You know, you're a little annoying
Maka, your dad loves you
Don't waste your breath on me
There's no way I'll ever consider you my father
Enough of that
Let's set the family feud aside for a moment
As you know, if a Meister and Weapon Pair collect 99 evil souls
Souls that have strayed and become Kishin eggs
And additionally collect the soul of one witch
Then the weapon will obtain the qualifications necessary to become a Death Scythe
One of my instruments
But it's that last soul that's a bit tricky
You've made it this far
But you should know there are countless Meisters who have lost their lives when they challenged a witch
You'll need to be very careful, Maka
But if you're lucky, maybe the Death Scythe you create will be as powerful as the one your mom created before you
Right
Also, please do be sure not to make any mistakes
This last collection, the witch's soul, is very important
If you slip up all of the 99 Kishin souls the two of you have collected so far will be confiscated
We understand, sir
Yeah, we'll make a clean job of it, no worries
In that case, I'll see you two later
Maka!
You are a bit annoying
If you don't shut up, I'm going to use my Reaper chop to split your head open
It's more effective if you warn before you chop
It's on you
Can you handle us?
So cool, baby, scandalous
Resonance of the soul
Will Soul Leader become a Death Scythe?
Now
I always get what I want. Just give it to me.
I'm a beauty beautiful pretty lady.
Come give my back a scrub.
But you know, you know, I've got a secret use I do.
Pumpkins. Pump, pumpkin. Pump, pumpkin.
Cause that's my magic spell. Pump, pumpkin. Pump, pumpkin.
This must be the house where the witch Blair lives.
A pumpkin house? That's cool.
It looks tasty, but sneaking into a house isn't very manly.
Why don't we just charge right in there?
We can't. She's different from the others we've faced so far.
Let's go.
Hey, come back here!
Naked lady!
Hey, what's the matter? Is everything okay down there in the bubbles, little boy?
It's okay. Cool guys see naked women all the time. I'm totally used to it.
Of course you are, dear. I'm sure that's why your nose is bleeding.
Yeah. Never mind. Your soul is mine.
You idiot! What were you thinking?
Sorry to interrupt, but I'll be taking your soul now.
I hope that cute boy will be alright.
Could you transform into a scythe?
Working on it, Maka.
Okay, that's it, witch lady. Naked or not, I'm still gonna eat your soul now.
Witch lady?
Oh, wow! He really became a scythe!
After I take your soul, he'll be much more. Soul will be a death scythe.
And I'll have created a weapon stronger than my dad.
I like it!
Why don't you be a good little girl and give it to me?
Pumpkin, pumpkin, pumpkin, Halloween cannon!
Wow, death scythe. You're a real frisky one, aren't you?
Oh, and I heard that you have a little daughter, too. Isn't that right?
What sort of girl is she?
You don't want to ask that. Trust me on this one.
Okay, but why?
Just in case you haven't figured it out yet, death scythe is a bit of a player.
And that didn't go over very well with his wife.
Huh?
They're in the process of getting a divorce right now.
The worst thing is his daughter, Maka, is on her mother's side. She hates it.
That sounds complicated.
Maka! Please don't hate me, Maka!
I love you and Mama! I promise, Maka!
It's true! It's true! I love you! I love you!
I love you!
Thank you very much, sir.
Bye, Mr. Death Scythe.
Please come again.
Yeah.
Bye!
Damn that witch. How am I supposed to be cool when she's all hot and naked like that, huh?
We expected a stiff attack. She is a witch, but you lost your chance to become a death scythe because you couldn't resist her.
You're just jealous of her boobs.
It's her. What now?
I'm thinking.
Huh?
Oh! My little scythe boy!
Listen up, Sol. This time I wrote down a detailed plan on this piece of paper.
And that's supposed to give us an edge this time? We aren't exactly going grocery shopping here.
A piece of paper isn't going to help us beat a witch.
Fine! Then you tell me what we need to do to beat Blair!
Who knows? I vote for brute force, though.
That's your answer for everything. We have to work together here or don't you want to become a death scythe?
Yeah, I get it, Maka. Shut up now.
We have to take this seriously.
This is the witch we're going up against.
Pumpkin?
Let's just follow my...
Hmm?
Halloween Cannon!
You should give it up. You can't beat me, girl.
What are you doing, you idiot?!
Shut up! Or were you just going to try beating her by getting a nosebleed again?
Men are completely useless sometimes. You only ran into Blair's house in the first place because you knew she was taking a bath.
Now you're just making false accusations. And would you tell me how girls always come up with these wild assumptions in the first place?
Hmph. Women's intuition.
I don't understand you sometimes.
Hey there, little sight boy. Is that dumb girl of yours giving you a hard time?
Why don't you forget about her and come be mine?
I would never, ever yell at you like she is no matter what you did to me.
Hold on, witch. I'm Sol's partner, not you, okay? Our conversations don't concern you.
Hmph. Is that so?
Well...
We'll see about that, girlie.
What the...
Some pumpkin pumpkin?
Smashing pumpkin!
What should we try now, Sol? My attacks won't work on her.
Sol?
Sol, hello?
What's wrong?
Why don't you forget about her and come be mine?
Hmph.
Good times at Chupacabras.
You're out drinking when your daughter's in trouble? What kind of father are you?
What? Maka? Something happened?
She's not doing so well against this witch. It looks like she might die.
What? Maka, hold on.
Stop right there. Think about what you're doing.
You or I could win against an opponent like that with one blow.
A single reaper chop is all it would take to crush a skull.
We both know that death sight.
But our skills aren't being tested right now.
You're her father. You must understand the situation.
Maka.
Still, there's something a little weird about that witch.
Sol, what's going on? I don't understand why you haven't been answering me.
Maka.
There you are.
Stop talking.
Hey, what did you draw me like that for?
I don't think we should be partners anymore, Maka. You see?
I only want to be witch Blair's weapon now.
Oh, do you really want me?
Yeah, that's more like it. Leave my daughter alone, you little scumbag.
Is now really the time to be saying that?
Blair!
You used your magic to make Sol want to be with you. That's a dirty trick.
You really are stupid.
Huh?
Any man would choose a girl with a body like Blair's over you and your flat chest.
She didn't have to trick me to make me pick her instead of you.
Now that you mention it, that witch does have a really nice body, doesn't she?
It would be best if you just shut up for a while.
You men.
All of you, you're horrible.
Cheating on every woman.
But you.
You I actually decided to trust.
I put my faith in you.
I can't believe this.
I wish that all of you would just die!
Hey, Sol.
You said that all women make wild assumptions without reasoning first, right?
That's what you said?
Well, what reason do men have for cheating?
It's not fair!
How am I supposed to know? I can't answer that.
After all, cool men don't cheat on their partners, do they?
Marka!
We've got them all. Good job.
Yes, Sol. Thank you for that.
In the end, the shape and form don't matter at all.
It's only the soul that matters, right? Nothing else.
Once you eat that...
That's right. With this soul, I'll become a Death Scythe.
Oh.
The power!
I can feel incredible power!
Or not.
Huh?
No way.
Meow!
Don't tell me.
You're not really...
I never said that I was a witch, did I?
You just made that assumption all on your own.
I'm really just a cat with a ridiculous amount of magical power.
Huh?
The shape and form don't matter, isn't that right?
Huh, Sol?
Yes, just as I suspected.
The cat'll do.
Yes, Blair, I'll be your cat toy any-
You've gotta be kidding me!
Does this mean I ate 99 human souls and one cat's soul? That just cannot be right!
And that's not all.
The witch's soul is very important.
If you slip up all of the 99 Kishin souls the two of you have collected so far will be confiscated.
All of them will be confiscated.
All confiscated.
So that means...
We've failed!
Dammit, dammit, dammit!
We have to start all over.
As the Meister, I'll take responsibility, okay?
Oh, man, and I was this close to being the coolest guy in the Academy!
You just ate your soul, you damn cat! What are you still doing up there?
You aren't very smart, are you, little girly? Don't you know that all cats have nine souls?
So, Sol, when are you gonna leave this dumb girl for me anyway?
Blair, go away! Stop following us, will ya?
Come on, Sol! You know you want to!
The situation isn't cool at all.
The boy's name is Blackstar.
He is an assassin shrouded in darkness.
With his partner, he stalks his enemies from the shadows.
Subaki, the head of the table. He's the target?
Yes. We're after Al Capone along with his associates.
About a hundred souls in all.
A hundred versus me. What I like.
Blackstar.
Those are Kishin souls down there, ones who have strayed out onto the path of evil.
We have to reclaim them all.
Blackstar.
He is the Meister who controls Tsubaki, the magic dark arm.
But this powerful young boy still has much to learn.
Let's go!
Prologue 2. Blackstar. Coming soon.
Well, festival this all was soot.
The beat is the sunне.
Connection of seeds.
ут the 국a tracksyon
The depth of dream matchings.
For the fate to take that spell.
And that's what we mean!
...
I冗談
The world is dark and contemplates
The air wścią is white as time as you
I've got to make a thinker to make tutaj
I promised that one day
We'll be right back.
I love it!
Well, it's tasty, for one thing.
On the next episode of Soul Eater, I am the star.
The big man is showing up here.
Watch it, or I'll take your soul.